Office of the President Jill Ker Conway Files, 1974-1985
Smith College Archives
- SERIES XV. NON-SMITH ORGANIZATIONS
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Economic Policy Council 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Economic Policy Council-Miscellaneous undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Educational Testing Service 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Educom 1978-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Elderhostel 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Freedom House Institute on Schools and Education 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Girl Guides and Girl Scouts, World Foundation for 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Girls Clubs of America 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hamilton Prize Competition 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education Resource Services 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education Strategic Planning Institute 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Architecture and Urban Studies 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Institute for the Study of Educational Policy 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Institute of World Affairs 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Association of University Presidents 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - IBM 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Chautauqua Society 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - John Minter Associates 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Juster Pope Associates, Architects & Planners 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - League of Women Voters 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of
    - -General 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - -Board of Higher Education 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - -Board of Regents of Higher Education 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - -Department of Education 1975-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - -Executive Office of Educational Affairs 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - -Health and Education Facilities Authority 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts Higher Education Assistance Corp. 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - MassPIRG (Box 8)
    See Series XVII. Students-Organizations-MassPIRG
  - Mellon Fellowship in the Humanities 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - National Association of Independent Schools 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems 1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - National Conference on Women, the Economy and Public Policy 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - National Conference on Women, the Economy and Public Policy-Phase I 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Council on Foreign Languages and International Studies 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - National Executive Service Corps 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Humanities Institute 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Independent Colleges and Universities 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - National Science Foundation 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - New England Association of Schools and Colleges
    - -General 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - -General 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - -Accreditation
      - -Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - -Information for Evaluation, Introduction 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - -Information for Evaluation, Sections I - VI 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - -Information for Evaluation, Sections VII - X 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - -Evaluation Report 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Fifth Year Interim Report 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -Five Colleges 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New England Board of Higher Education 1977-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - New England Colleges Fund 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - New England Colleges Fund 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New England Colleges Fund 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New England Colleges Fund 1984 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New England Colleges Fund 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New England Council, Inc. 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New England Council of Latin American Studies 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New England Low-level Radiation [NELRAD] 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - New England Regional Computing Program [NERCOMP] 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Organization Plus 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1975-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Project HERS (Higher Education Resource Services) (Box 10)
    See Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Committee for Concerns of Women in New England Colleges and Universities
  - Rhodes Scholarship Trust 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Schenkman Publishing Company 1980-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Selfhelp Community Services 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sigma Xi 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Smithsonian Institute 1981, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - United Nations Association, Economic Policy Council 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - United States Government (Box 11)
    - -General (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - -Commission on White House Fellowships (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - -Department of Education 1975-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      See also Administrative Issues-Legislation/Legislators-U.S. Department of Education
    - -Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1975-1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - -Department of Health and Human Services 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - -Department of Labor 1976-1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - -United States Military Academy, West Point 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - United Way 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - United Way 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - William T. Grant Foundation 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - World Affairs Council of the Connecticut Valley 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 11)
    - -A 1976-1985 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - -B (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - -Ca-Ci ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - -Co-Cr ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - -D-F ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - -G-H ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - -I ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - -J-M ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - -N ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - -O-R ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - -S-U ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - -V-Z ca. 1975-1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- SERIES XVI. SPEECHES
  The records in this series are filed chronologically by event and are labeled with one or all of the following: title, location, and event.
  The duties of the President included many public speaking engagements, not only at Smith College events but also at local and national gatherings. The records in this series include notes and some full texts for many of these speeches, as well as associated correspondence and newspaper clippings.
  More detailed information about the events themselves can be found in the Events and Engagements series, and in some cases in the records of sponsoring Smith Administrative Offices, Academic Departments, Committees and Boards, or Non-Smith Organizations.
  - First Speech as President-Elect? ca. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Smith Welcome to Freshmen and Parents Jul 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Smith School for Social Work Fall 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 7 Sep 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wheaton College-Alice Emerson Inauguration 20 Sep 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Smith Inaugural 19 Oct 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Montclair Kimberley Academy Bicentennial 20 Apr 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Smith Last Chapel May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Smith Alumnae Fund Conference Sep 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 8 Sep 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Smith Capital Campaign Conference 28 Sep 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Smith Last Chapel May 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 8 Sep 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Smith Alumnae Council Oct 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - IBM, Acapulco-"Women's Place: Modernization and Tech. Change" 8 May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Smith Last Chapel 19 May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Girls Clubs of America-"A Proper Perspective" Jun 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Harvard Graduate Society 7 Jun 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 10 Sep 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Senate Committee on Human Resources-"An Overview of Conditions, Problems and Prospects Affecting American Women" 1 Feb 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Smith Senior Class Meeting 15 Feb 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Smith Last Chapel 18 May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Wellesley College-Research Conference on Educational Environments and the Undergraduate Woman 13 Sep 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Smith Helen Hills Hills Chapel Anniversary-"A Journey in Time" 16 Sep 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Smith Opening Convocation Sep 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Olin Fellows Program Conference Sep 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Smith Freshman Colloquia 3 Oct 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Smith Margaret Sanger Centennial Conference 13 Nov 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - College Board 11 Feb 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Portsmouth Abbey Commencement May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Smith Last Chapel 16 May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Women & Social Change Lecture-"A Redefinition of Standard Historical Explanations of Social Change…" 3 Jun 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Loomis Chaffee Commencement 6 Jun 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Smith Management Program 27 Jul 1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Northfield/Mt. Hermon Installation of Richard Unsworth as Headmaster 12 Oct 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Smith Opening Convocation Sep 1980 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Smith Club of California-Symposium 12 Nov 1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Smith Club of Houston-Alumnae Association Centennial 22 Jan 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Smith Spectrum Spring 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Smith Last Chapel 22 May 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Amer. Assoc. Of University Women-Perspective on the Second Century" 25 Jun 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Smith Freshman Meeting 3 Sep 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 8 Sep 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Australian Embassy 24 Sep 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Madeira School, Greenwich, VA-75th Anniversary 1 Oct 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Boston College-Library Dedication 18 Oct 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Independent School Association of Massachusetts 19 Nov 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Laurentian University-Falcon Bridge Lecture 11 Jan 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Smith Second Semester Opening 26 Jan 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Smith Conference-Ethics in Medicine and Science 4 Mar 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Brown University-Pembroke Center Opening 11 Mar 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Colony Club 18 Mar 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mount Holyoke Sesquicentennial 2 Apr 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Smith Rally for Educational Rights 13 Apr 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Smith Conference-Music in Paris in the 1830s 15 Apr 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Smith Last Chapel 21 May 1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Foxcroft School Commencement 4 Jun 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Smith Alumnae Council 14 Oct 1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Middlebury College-"19th-Century Origins of Education for Women" 4 Nov 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Wabash College Centennial 1 May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Smith Last Chapel 20 May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Smith Management Program-Management Education Conference Jul 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy Foundation Conference 13 Aug 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 6 Sep 1983 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Smith Lecture-Dalai Lama Introduction 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Westover School 75th Anniversary 12 May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Smith Opening Convocation 9 Sep 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - University of Maine Opening Convocation 11 Sep 1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Queens University at Kingston-The Mission of the University Oct 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Cambridge Forum-"Is Higher Education Conquering Sexism?" 24 Oct 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - University of Toronto-Fall Convocation 22 Nov 1984 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Radcliffe College-Graduate Society Medal Spring 1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Women's National Democratic Club-"A Feminist Agenda for the 90s" 9 May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Smith Last Chapel 17 May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Source Material 1973-1982, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Unidentified undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
- SERIES XVII. STUDENTS
  The records in this series document the relationship of the Smith student body with the faculty and administration of the college. There are records about student organizations, publications, athletics, and other activities.
  Information about students can also be found in the records of Committees and Boards with student representation, in the Administrative Offices series in the records of the Dean of the College and the Dean of Students, as well as in the records of specific student residences in the Buildings and Grounds series.
  - Academic Awards
    - -Ruth Forbes Prize for Poetry 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -Hatfield Memorial Award for English 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Knowles Scholarship 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Jeanne McFarland Prize 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -Mendenhall History Prize 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol & Drugs (Box 1)
    See also Series V. Administrative Offices-Dean of Students-Assistant Dean -and- Series IX. Committees & Boards-Alcohol Task Force
  - Athletics
    See also Series II. Academic Departments-Exercise and Sport Studies
    - -General 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -General 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -General 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -General 1984-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Facilities & Equipment Use 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -Aikido 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Basketball 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Crew 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -Field Hockey 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - -Riding 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -Riding 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - -Rugby 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Ski Club 1977, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - -Swimming 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Swimming-Broenniman & FitzPatrick Channel Swim 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Deaths, Recognition of [at commencement, etc] 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Identification Numbers (Box 2)
    See Series IV. Admin. Issues-Administrative Structure (1976)
  - Grievances 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Japan America Student Conference 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minority Students (Box 2)
    See Subject Guide-Race
  - Organizations
    - -General 1976-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -General-Space Problem 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Academic Honor Board 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - -AISEC 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - -Asian Students Association 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Athletic Association 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Baha'I 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -Black Students' Alliance 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Classes 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -Debating Club 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - -ERA Task Force 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -International Affairs Organization 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Judicial Board 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -Lesbian Alliance 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -MASSPIRG 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Outing Club 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Phi Beta Kappa (Box 3)
      See Series XV. Non-Smith Organizations-Phi Beta Kappa
    - -Peer Support and Information 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Recreation Council 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Scholarship Loan Library 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -Senior Prank Committee 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -SOS [Service Organizations of Smith] 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      See also Series V. Admin. Offices-Chapel
    - -SOS [Service Organizations of Smith] 1981-1985, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - -Smiffenpoofs 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - -Smithereens 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - -Southern Africa Support Committee 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - -Student Government Association
      - -General 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - -General 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - -General 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - -Finance Committee 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - -Lecture Committee 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - -Quality of Life Committee 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -S.T.A.R.T. Committee 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - -Women's Resource Center 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Publications
    - -General 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -New Current 1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -Sophian 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Yearbook 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Radio Station 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Senior Class Gifts 1976-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sexual Harassment (Box 4)
  - Spring Break 1978 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Statistics (Box 4)
    See Series XV. Non-Smith Orgs-Cooperative Institutional Research Program
  - Student Centers
    - -Davis Student Center 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - -Mwangi Cultural Center 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      See also: Series XVII. Students-Student Organizations-BSA (1983)
  - Violence Against
    - -General 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - -Rape, Legal Implications 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- SERIES XVIII. PHOTOGRAPHS
  The photographs in this series document many of the events and activities described in the printed material.
  Additional photographs may be found in the Smith College Archives collections which document specific events, such as Honorary Degree presentations, Ivy Day and Commencement. Please note that slides are not included in the photograph listing, as they have been integrated into the Archives' general slide collection. Please ask the reference archivist if you wish to see slides.
  - Portraits (Box 1)
    - -by Cooney, Gabriel 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -by Cooney, Gabriel 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -by Cooney, Gabriel undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -by Daniels, Gordon 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -by Gill, W. Allan Jul 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -by Kidd, Chuck 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -by Marshall, Karen undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Photographer Unknown Jan 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -Oil Portraits by Sarah Swenson 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Miscellaneous ca. 1974-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Family-John Conway undated. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alumnae ca. 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    See also: Series XVIII. Photographs-Events-Smith-Ivy Day, -Miscellaneous, and -Panels
  - Donors ca. 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Events
    - -Smith
      - -Commencement 1976-1985, undated. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - -Convocation 1975-1984, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - -Conway Celebration Day
        - -General 17 Apr 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - -Gazebo 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - -Miscellaneous Apr 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - -Inauguration (Box 2)
        - -General Oct 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - -Crowd and Choir Oct 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - -Speakers Oct 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Ivy Day 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - -Last Chapel 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -Panels ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Rally Day ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -Smith College Medal Ceremony ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - -Miscellaneous ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Non-Smith ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty, Staff, and Administration ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Faculty, Staff, and Administration-Thomas C. Mendenhall 1974, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Intercollegiate Associations ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Intercollegiate Associations-AICUM 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Students ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    See also: Series XVIII. Photographs-Portraits-by Kidd, Chuck
  - Post-Smith 1986- (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous ca. 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)